## **Steven Geudens**

2440, Geel +32 474 348 124

Geudens.Steven@outlook.com https://steven-geudens.be

https://www.linkedin.com/in/steven-geudens

.I am a **motivated** person who is constantly seeking opportunities to improve my knowledge and skills. New challenges energize me, and I am always **eager to learn**.

I can function well both independently and in a team.

In addition, I am also a **perfectionist** and strive to do everything in the right way. The idea of having done something in the best possible way gives me a lot of satisfaction.

My main hobby is fitness, which I have been actively engaged in since 2018. This indicates that I have some perseverance.

### Work experience

### Intern CIAM IoT development

02/2021 to 06/2021

IdentIT

2550, Kontich

Development of a set-top box secured using the ForgeRock IoT SDKs.

More information about this assignment can be found on the IdentIT website via the following link: <a href="https://www.identit.eu/job/internship-secure-a-tv-platform">https://www.identit.eu/job/internship-secure-a-tv-platform</a>

### Intern MS Power Apps development

02/2023 to 05/2023

Janssen Pharmaceuticals N.V.

2340, Beerse

Development of an application using the MS Power Platform (Power Apps, Power Automate, Power BI).

### Intern MS Power Apps development

07/2023 to 07/2023

Janssen Pharmaceuticals N.V.

2340, Beerse

Development of an application using the MS Power Platform (Power Apps, Power Automate, Power BI).

### Skills

# Hard Skills HTML Perfectionist CSS Teamplayer Javascript (React, Angular) Agile C# (.NET, ASP.NET) Eager to learn SQL Problem-solving way of thinking NoSQL Git and GitHub REST

### Language

**Dutch:** Very good**English:** Very good

### Education

### **Sint Jozef Geel**

High school or equivalent Electrical installations 2440, Geel

Achieved on 06/2019

### **Thomas More Geel**

Graduate System- and Network management 2440, Geel

# Achieved on 06/2021

**Thomas More Geel** 

Graduate Programming

### 2440, Geel

Achieved on 06/2023